twinstrangers.net 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy

**SECTION 1 - INFORMATION CONSENT**

When you provide us with personal information on registration you consent to the collection and use of this information for the specific reason of finding a Twin Stranger.

If we request personal information for a secondary reason, for example for marketing purposes, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, and/or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my Information Consent?

If having registered, you then change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to disclose your personal information and/ or to contact you and, by contacting us at Info@twinstrangers.com or mailing us at:

Vision Independent Productions 26/27 Finglas, Business Pk. Dublin. Ireland

**SECTION 2 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

When you register with Twin Strangers we collect the personal information you give such as your full name, email address and your photograph.

We will only share your photograph with other users on our Digital Platforms.

Your name and contact details can only be shared with a particular user when you give us express permission to do so.

We also automatically receive your computer's internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

From time to time we may send you emails with Twin Strangers Updates.

By using this service you acknowledge that a "Twin Match" is not guaranteed.

**SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE**

We will only disclose your personal information where we are legally required to do so, or in the event that you violate our Terms of Service, or where you give us permission to do so.

**SECTION 4 - SECURITY**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

**SECTION 5 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the WEB Site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of any modifications concernng what information we collect, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If the Twin Strangers Digital platform is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to operate Twin Strangers.

**QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you wish to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information on the Site, register a complaint, or simply seek more information, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at Info@TwinStrangers.com or by mail at Vision Independent Productions:

26/27 Finglas Business Pk. Tolka Valley Rd. Dublin. Ireland.
